(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{17:function(t,e,o){},19:function(t,e,o){"use strict";o.r(e);var i=o(0),r=o.n(i),n=o(5),a=o.n(n),c=o(1),s=o(2),p=o(3),u=o.n(p);var d=function(t){var e=t.setStop,o=t.setTimer,n=t.timer,a=Object(s.a)(u.a),p=Object(c.a)(a,1)[0];return Object(i.useEffect)(function(){var t=setInterval(function(){o(function(t){return t-1})},1e3);return function(){clearInterval(t)}},[o]),Object(i.useEffect)(function(){0===n&&(p(),e(!0)),document.querySelector(".timer").style.opacity=n>100?0:1},[n,p,e]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"timer"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"countDown"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,n)))},l=o(6),h=o.n(l);var O=function(t){var e=t.currentQuestionNumber,o=t.data,n=t.setCurrentQuestionNumber,a=t.amountWon,p=t.stop,l=t.setStop,O=Object(i.useState)(null),m=Object(c.a)(O,2),f=m[0],b=m[1],y=Object(i.useState)("option"),v=Object(c.a)(y,2),g=v[0],j=v[1],w=Object(i.useState)(!0),N=Object(c.a)(w,2),q=N[0],S=N[1],E=Object(i.useState)(45),k=Object(c.a)(E,2),M=k[0],C=k[1],T=Object(s.a)(h.a),A=Object(c.a)(T,1)[0],W=Object(s.a)(u.a),B=Object(c.a)(W,1)[0],I=Object(i.useState)(null),P=Object(c.a)(I,2),D=P[0],H=P[1];return Object(i.useEffect)(function(){H(o[e-1])},[e,o]),r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},D&&q&&!p?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz"},r.a.createElement(d,{timer:M,setTimer:C,setStop:l}),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quizSection"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},D&&D.question),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"chooseOption"},D&&D.options.map(function(t,o){return r.a.createElement("div",{key:o,className:f===t?g:"option",onClick:function(){return function(t){b(t),j("option active"),setTimeout(function(){t.correct?(j("option correct"),C(1e7),setTimeout(function(){A(),n(function(t){return t+1}),C(e<=3?45:e>=4&&e<=8?60:1e7)},3e3)):(j("option wrong"),setTimeout(function(){B()},[3e3]),setTimeout(function(){S(!1)},4e3))},1e3)}(t)}},t.Option)})))):r.a.createElement("div",{className:"endTextContainer"},r.a.createElement("h1",{className:"endText"},r.a.createElement("span",null,"You Earned : "),r.a.createElement("span",null," \u20b9 ",a)))))};var m=function(t){var e=t.currentQuestionNumber,o=t.pyramid;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"pyramid"},o.map(function(t,o){return r.a.createElement("div",{key:o,className:e===t.id?"pyramidItem active":"pyramidItem"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"index"},t.id),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"money"}," \u20b9",t.amount))}))},f=(o(17),o(7)),b=o.n(f),y=[{id:1,question:"Grand Central Terminal, Park Avenue, New York is the world's",options:[{Option:"largest railway station",correct:!0},{Option:"highest railway station",correct:!1},{Option:"longest railway station",correct:!1},{Option:"None of the these",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:'Which of the following god known as "Gauri Nandan"?',options:[{Option:"Agni",correct:!1},{Option:"Indra",correct:!1},{Option:"Hanuman",correct:!1},{Option:"Ganesha",correct:!0}]},{id:3,question:"Who gave the equation of Force F = ma ?",options:[{Option:"Newton",correct:!0},{Option:"Einstein",correct:!1},{Option:"Tesla",correct:!1},{Option:"C.V. Raman",correct:!1}]},{id:4,question:"Which of these terms can only be used for women?",options:[{Option:" Dirghaayu",correct:!1},{Option:"Suhagan",correct:!0},{Option:"Chiranjeevi",correct:!1},{Option:"Sushil",correct:!1}]},{id:5,question:"Which of these spices is the smallest in size?",options:[{Option:"Ajwain",correct:!0},{Option:"Jeera",correct:!1},{Option:"Saunf",correct:!1},{Option:"Methi Seeds",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:"Which battle in 1757 marked the beginning of British occupation in India?",options:[{Option:"Assaye",correct:!1},{Option:"Plassey",correct:!0},{Option:"Buxar",correct:!1},{Option:"Cuddalore",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"Which is the second most spoken language of Nepal?",options:[{Option:"Bajjika",correct:!1},{Option:"Nepali",correct:!1},{Option:"Maithili",correct:!0},{Option:"Bhojpuri",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"In which of these two sports is the term 'free hit' used?",options:[{Option:"Football, Squash",correct:!1},{Option:"Badminton, Tennis",correct:!1},{Option:" Badminton, Cricket",correct:!1},{Option:"Hockey, Cricket",correct:!0}]},{id:9,question:"Which of these medical conditions is most likely to cause dehydration?",options:[{Option:"Malaria",correct:!1},{Option:"Tetanus",correct:!1},{Option:"Diarrhoea",correct:!0},{Option:" Beriberi",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"Who is the only MP in the current Lok Sabha who is also an Olympic medalist?",options:[{Option:"Abhinav Bindra",correct:!1},{Option:"Rajyavardan Singh Rathore",correct:!0},{Option:"Karnam Maleshwari",correct:!1},{Option:"Gagan Narang",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:" In which state is the Larji Hydroelectric Power Project located?",options:[{Option:"Uttarakhand",correct:!1},{Option:"Jammu and Kashmir",correct:!1},{Option:"Sikkim",correct:!1},{Option:"Himachal Pradesh",correct:!0}]},{id:12,question:"Whose autobiography is titled 'Man of Everest' also published as 'Tiger of the snows'?",options:[{Option:"Sir Edmund Hillary",correct:!1},{Option:"Tenzing Norgay",correct:!0},{Option:"George Mallory",correct:!1},{Option:"Major H P S Aluhwalia",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"Who recently became the first woman director in the board of Reliance Industries?",options:[{Option:"Kokilaben Ambani",correct:!1},{Option:"Deepti Salgaonkar",correct:!1},{Option:"Nitu Ambani",correct:!0},{Option:"Nina Kothari",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"Where was Indian diplomat Devyani Khobragade posted when she was arrested in a visa case in 2013?",options:[{Option:"England",correct:!1},{Option:"USA",correct:!0},{Option:"Switzerland",correct:!1},{Option:"Russia",correct:!1}]},{id:15,question:"What discovered in Assam in 1823, is credited to the British official Robert Bruce ?",options:[{Option:"Oil",correct:!1},{Option:"Tea",correct:!0},{Option:"Murga silk",correct:!1},{Option:"Jute",correct:!1}]},{id:16,question:" The International Literacy Day is observed on",options:[{Option:"Sep 8",correct:!0},{Option:"Nov 28",correct:!1},{Option:"May 2",correct:!1},{Option:"Sep 22",correct:!1}]},{id:17,question:"The language of Lakshadweep. a Union Territory of India, is",options:[{Option:"Tamil",correct:!1},{Option:"Hindi",correct:!1},{Option:"Malayam",correct:!0},{Option:"Telugu",correct:!1}]},{id:18,question:"In which group of places the Kumbha Mela is held every twelve years?",options:[{Option:"Ujjain, Purl, Prayag, Haridwar",correct:!1},{Option:"Prayag, Haridwar, Ujjain, Nasik",correct:!0},{Option:"Rameshwaram, Purl, Badrinath, Dwarika",correct:!1},{Option:"Chittakoot, Ujjain, Prayag, Haridwar",correct:!1}]},{id:19,question:"Bahubali festival is related to",options:[{Option:"Islam",correct:!1},{Option:"Hinduism",correct:!1},{Option:"Buddhism",correct:!1},{Option:"Jainism",correct:!0}]},{id:20,question:"Which day is observed as the World Standards  Day?",options:[{Option:"June 26",correct:!1},{Option:"Oct 14",correct:!0},{Option:"Nov 15",correct:!1},{Option:"Dec 2",correct:!1}]},{id:21,question:"Kalarippayat is the martial art  of the State of",options:[{Option:"Madhya Pradesh",correct:!1},{Option:"Mizoram",correct:!1},{Option:"Nagaland",correct:!1},{Option:"Kerala",correct:!0}]},{id:22,question:"Which city of India was first of all affected by plague?",options:[{Option:"Jaipur",correct:!1},{Option:"Bombay",correct:!1},{Option:"Surat",correct:!0},{Option:"Kanpur",correct:!1}]},{id:23,question:"Industrial Toxicology- Research Centre, is situated in which of the following states? ",options:[{Option:"Uttar Pradesh",correct:!0},{Option:"Gujarat",correct:!1},{Option:"Madhya Pradesh",correct:!1},{Option:"Bihar",correct:!1}]},{id:24,question:"Ghototkach in Mahabharat was the son of",options:[{Option:"Duryodhana",correct:!1},{Option:"Arjuna",correct:!1},{Option:"Yudhishthir",correct:!1},{Option:"Bhima",correct:!0}]},{id:25,question:"Which of the followiing is a folk dance of India?",options:[{Option:"Kathakali",correct:!1},{Option:"Mohiniattam",correct:!1},{Option:"Garba",correct:!0},{Option:"Manipuri",correct:!1}]},{id:26,question:"Central Salt and Marine Chemicals Research Institute is located at",options:[{Option:"Ahmedabad",correct:!1},{Option:"Bhavnagar",correct:!1},{Option:"Gandhinagar",correct:!1},{Option:"Panaji",correct:!0}]},{id:27,question:"The 227 year old 'Nawab Saheb Ki Haveli' is Iocated at",options:[{Option:"Hyderabad",correct:!1},{Option:"Jaipur",correct:!0},{Option:"New Delhi",correct:!1},{Option:"Agra",correct:!1}]},{id:28,question:"The dates of National Calendar Permanently correspond with the",options:[{Option:"Vikrami Calendar",correct:!1},{Option:"Mohammadan Calendar",correct:!1},{Option:"Georgian Calendar",correct:!0},{Option:"None of these",correct:!1}]},{id:29,question:"Which of the-following is wrongly matched?",options:[{Option:"Qutab Minar- Delhi",correct:!1},{Option:"Taj Mahal -Agra",correct:!1},{Option:"Ajanta Caves -Maharashtra",correct:!1},{Option:"Charminar -Lucknow",correct:!0}]},{id:30,question:"Good Friday' is observed to commemorate the event of",options:[{Option:"Birth of Jesus Christ",correct:!1},{Option:"Birth of' St. Peter",correct:!1},{Option:"Crucification 'of Jesus Christ",correct:!0},{Option:"Rebirth of Jesus Christ",correct:!1}]},{id:31,question:"Which of the following is observed as Sports Day every year?",options:[{Option:"22nd April",correct:!1},{Option:"26th  july",correct:!1},{Option:"29th August",correct:!0},{Option:"2nd October",correct:!1}]},{id:32,question:"World Health Day is observed on",options:[{Option:"April 7",correct:!0},{Option:"March 6",correct:!1},{Option:"March 15",correct:!1},{Option:"April 28",correct:!1}]},{id:33,question:"Pongal is a popular festival of which state?",options:[{Option:"Karnataka",correct:!1},{Option:"Kerala",correct:!1},{Option:"Tamil Nadu",correct:!0},{Option:"Andhra Pradesh",correct:!1}]},{id:34,question:"The first month of the Indian national calendar is",options:[{Option:"Magha",correct:!1},{Option:"Chaitra",correct:!0},{Option:"Ashadha",correct:!1},{Option:"Vaishakha",correct:!1}]}];var v=function(t){var e=t.setStart;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"username"},r.a.createElement("button",{className:"submitBtn",onClick:function(){e(!0)}},"Start"))};var g=function(){var t=Object(i.useState)(1),e=Object(c.a)(t,2),o=e[0],n=e[1],a=Object(i.useState)("0"),p=Object(c.a)(a,2),u=p[0],d=p[1],l=Object(i.useState)(!1),h=Object(c.a)(l,2),f=h[0],g=h[1],j=Object(i.useState)(!1),w=Object(c.a)(j,2),N=w[0],q=w[1],S=Object(s.a)(b.a),E=(Object(c.a)(S,1)[0],Object(i.useMemo)(function(){return[{id:15,amount:"7,00,00,000"},{id:14,amount:"1,00,00,000"},{id:13,amount:"50,00,000"},{id:12,amount:"25,00,000"},{id:11,amount:"12,50,000"},{id:10,amount:"6,40,000"},{id:9,amount:"3,20,000"},{id:8,amount:"1,60,000"},{id:7,amount:"80,000"},{id:6,amount:"40,000"},{id:5,amount:"20,000"},{id:4,amount:"10,000"},{id:3,amount:"5000"},{id:2,amount:"2000"},{id:1,amount:"1000"}]},[]));return Object(i.useEffect)(function(){o>1&&d(E.find(function(t){return t.id===o-1}).amount)},[o,E]),Object(i.useEffect)(function(){!function(t){for(var e,o=t.length;0!==o;){e=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),o--;var i=[t[e],t[o]];t[o]=i[0],t[e]=i[1]}}(y),console.log(y)},[]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},N?r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(O,{data:y,stop:f,setStop:g,currentQuestionNumber:o,setCurrentQuestionNumber:n,amountWon:u,setAmountWon:d}),r.a.createElement(m,{stop:f,setStop:g,pyramid:E,currentQuestionNumber:o})):r.a.createElement(v,{setStart:q}))};a.a.createRoot(document.getElementById("root")).render(r.a.createElement(g,null))},3:function(t,e,o){t.exports=o.p+"static/media/wrong.e55862ad.mp3"},6:function(t,e,o){t.exports=o.p+"static/media/correct.d27f45ad.mp3"},7:function(t,e,o){t.exports=o.p+"static/media/play.3d8ba0a6.mp3"},8:function(t,e,o){t.exports=o(19)}},[[8,3,1]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.9312e3f1.chunk.js.map